http://www.cac.co.nz/terms-privacy-policy

LOGIN
NZ 03 359 2121 (INTL +64 3 359 2121)Terms & Privacy Policy
Canterbury Aero Club respects the privacy of its users. The following privacy policy is designed to inform you, as a user of this website, about the types of information that we may gather or collect from you in connection with your use of our website. It also is intended to explain the conditions under which Canterbury Aero Club uses and discloses that information, and your rights in relation to that information. Each time you use our website, the current version of this privacy policy will apply.
BY USING OR ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
Children
Canterbury Aero Club does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.
What Information Do We Collect?
At the time of registration a user will need to submit the following information: full name, email address, a valid password, registration date, last visit date, purchase history, and IP address. Canterbury Aero Club is not involved in any way of the collection of this data, it is submitted solely by the user. No other information is required or collected at the time of registration or any at any other time or process of our website. This information is used to personalize a user's experience on our website and for occasional communication. This information is stored on an encrypted web server, and is not shared with any outside party with the exception of email addresses for newsletter correspondence (see Shared Information). This information is used to enable us to provide service to our customers, and maintain the security of their accounts.
Shared Information
Canterbury Aero Club does not share any user related information with any third party companies except for email addresses which are used solely for newsletter correspondence, which the user agrees to at the time of registration. Email addresses will be imported/exported using constantcontact.com, a mass emailing website, to use as acommunication tool with our members.
Financial Information
Any financial information such as credit card numbers are kept with our third-party payment processor: PayPal. Canterbury Aero Club does not store or request any financial information for any reason.
Security
We take security of your information, such as name and email address, very seriously and use reasonable electronic, personnel, and physical measures to protect it from loss, theft, alteration, or misuse. We work to protect your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that you provide online at our Web Site
Google Analytics
We do utilize Google Analytics on our website, as part of doing business. We use information gathered by Google Analytics to better understand our customers' needs and to detect any issues users are having with our websites.
Right of Removal
If you would like to request to have your personal information removed from our servers, you may do so within your account profile or by submitting a request via our Contact Page. All requests will be addressed within the time frame required under GDPR policies. Keep in mind that removing your data is permanent and will result in the cancellation of any currently-active services without refund, as well as any Member Bonuses.
Web Cookies
A Web Cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user's computer, and that the user's browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the site. Canterbury Aero Club's website will store cookies on user's machines to track membership durations, active logins. No personal information is recorded or collected at this time, it is simply used for normal membership processes of the website.
Here at the Canterbury Aero Club, we provide a wide variety of training. From Introductory flights to Commercial Licenses, we do it all!
Address: Harewood Aviation Park25 Aviation DriveChristchurch International Airport7676 New Zealand
Phone: 03 359 2121 (+64 3 359 2121 if calling outside New Zealand) Fax: 03 359 2621 (+64 3 359 2621 if outside New Zealand)bookings@cac.co.nz
HomeMembers LoginShop CheckoutMy Shop AccountTerms & Privacy PolicyArchive
HomeAbout UsOur HistoryOur BasesOur PeopleOur FleetWebcam 1 – North EastWebcam 2 – North WestWebcam 3 – SouthLet's FlyTrainingRequirements to Gain a PPLGo FurtherMountain/CommercialRenewals/InternationalTheoryFaqsFlying By-Laws and RulesActivitiesShopNewsLatest NewsletterCAC News FlyerCareersContact
